Netanya, Israel **3**: 055 66 80 262

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a self-taught Junior Front-End Developer. I have experience developing full-stack applications (MVC architecture, API) following best practices (refactoring, code standards). I have deep foundations in Javascript.

I am a self-teaching individual at the core, passionate, motivated and dedicated to coding. Started as a digital marketer (google adwords & facebook ads) then worked as a QA in an automation testing team at Checkpoint (Jsystem automation testing framework) and took a 3 months' intensive course to study Javascript and the MEAN/MERN stack to kickstart my new career.

PROJECTS

BababoxTV built using Wordpress

<u>The Home Cook Hackathon project.</u> built using Node, Angularjs and MongoDB <u>My Portfolio</u> built using JS/HTML/CSS

EDUCATION

Intensive Coding Bootcamp — Elevation Academy — 2017 (3months)

Master Degree with honors — Business School — ISG Paris — 2007-2012

Bachelors of Science — Physics with honors — College Yabne Paris — 2007

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Checkpoint, Tel Aviv

Automation Testing Team | 2017 – 2018

Duties and Responsibilities

- Performing daily Automation Testing on JSystem (framework based on Java)
- Implement automation-first strategy. Maintain, expand, and improve our automated testing framework
- Work with Automation team to triage and identify bugs, collaborate with development team to develop comprehensive testing plan
- Perform product releases
- Stay up-to-date with new testing tools and test strategies (Kibana) and improve efficiency
- Extensive use of Jira management tool to report and track bugs.
- CCSA/CCSE certifications
- Extensive use of Linux command line

Elevation Academy, Tel Aviv

Junior Developer | Coding Bootcamp | Apr., 2017 – Jun., 2017

Duties and Responsibilities

- Led two Hackathons teams building projects using MEAN stack technologies
- Developed freelance projects: building landing pages from psd to html/CSS/JavaScript (mobile/tablet responsive)
- Deep Foundations in Javascript.

Digital Marketing Career

Digital Marketing Manager at Deloitte, Bill Tornade and Gigaspaces Technologies | 2014 –2017 Duties and Responsibilities

- Organization of events on the French territory
- Leading of Facebook and LinkedIn ads campaigns
- SEO and SEM Optimization
- Extensive use of automation tools (Salesforce, Sales Genius, Rainking...)

AREAS OF EXPERTISE:

Front-End Development
QA Automation Testing
Network Security
Networks & Systems Security
Virtualization and Cloud
Network Architecture
Digital Marketing

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

HTML

CSS

Javascript

React

Angular

REST

MERN

MEAN

Jira

Linux

Windows

Git

Wordpress

LANGUAGES SPOKEN:

French: Native English: Fluent Hebrew: Advanced

EXTRA-ACTIVITIES:

-Crypto and Blockchain -Advisor for Blockchain Decentralized Projects